<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dmitry&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://mylh.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dmitry&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Dmitry S. aka mylh</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mylh.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Georginify - Firefox Extension to learn Georgian</title>
      <link>https://mylh.me/posts/georginify-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mylh.me/posts/georginify-extension/</guid>
      <description>Due to the war in Ukraine I recently moved to Georgia and the first big issue I faced was Georgian alphabet. They don&amp;rsquo;t use Latin or Cyrillic charaters so I needed to learn it to be able to read and study Georgian language. To say the truth I always liked their characters - they are really nice, looke for your self: ყოველთვის მომწონდა ქართული ანბანი :) But for an unprepared person, they are almost indistinguishable from each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Stopped Using Facebook</title>
      <link>https://mylh.me/posts/delete-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 22:10:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mylh.me/posts/delete-facebook/</guid>
      <description>I was an ordinary Facebook user, not very social one - had a handful of &amp;ldquo;friends&amp;rdquo;, almost never posted or liked anything, mostly consumed newsfeed of people and groups I was subscribed to. I had an Instagram account where shared private photos with my friends. And I used Whatsapp as my primary messenger to communicate with everyone - family, friends, colleagues and other people I know.
All was good for many years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mylh.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 10:54:57 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mylh.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Dmitry - a father of three, programmer and music lover.
My Profession I write computer programs since 1990s and enjoy this activity so much that it became my main work for a lifetime. Worked with many languages - C/C++, Java, PHP, Haskell and others but fall in love with Python for its power to implement my ideas in fastest way possible. My second favorite language is Go, when I need to do a task that requires super high performance this is the language of my choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Simulation for QA</title>
      <link>https://mylh.me/posts/txn-backtesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 17:29:29 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mylh.me/posts/txn-backtesting/</guid>
      <description>How many tests we need to run to be sure that there are no errors introduced because of changes we made? This is the question we are going to answer using probabilistic simulations. Real life example from my work. We did it for TXN backtesting.
What Is TXN Backtesting TXN stands for Transaction check - which is a monitoring tool that executes several action steps in headless Chrome instance on our check servers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
